# CAMILLE OCAMPO

## **Fullstack Software Engineer**

cocampo0915@gmail.com | (818) 634-8535 | Los Angeles, CA github.com/cocampo0915 | linkedin.com/in/camille-ocampo

### **SUMMARY**

I am a full stack software engineer with strong analytical and problem solving skills, with experience in product development, process improvement, and project management. I am driven by a growth mindset to always continue learning and challenge myself to make a positive impact through my career and deliver high quality products to users.

### **SKILLS**

Languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Python

Libraries & Frameworks: jQuery, Node.js, Mongoose.js, Express.js, React.js, Django, Bootstrap, Materialize

**Databases:** MongoDB, PostgreSQL, GraphQL **Version Control/Deployment:** Git, Github, Netlify, Heroku

Methodologies: OOP, Functional, RESTful Routing, AJAX, MVC

Operating System: MacOS, Windows

Soft Skills: Excellent written and verbal communication skills.

Strong analytical skills for data driven decision making.

Excellent interpersonal and leadership skills to build key working relationships and facilitate collaboration.

#### **PROJECTS**

### **ALITR** - github.com/cocampo0915/ALITR

- A full stack web application that functions as a sort of to-do list, similar to a travel bucket list but with a focus on food destinations.
- Employs the following technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Express.js, Mongoose, MongoDB, EJS

## **LEVELUP Apparel** - github.com/cocampo0915/LEVELUP-Apparel---frontend

- A full stack web application that functions as a sort of to-do list, similar to a travel bucket list but with a focus on food destinations.
- Employs the following technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Express.js, Mongoose, MongoDB, EJS

### **Gastronaut** - github.com/cocampo0915/Gastronaut

- A full stack web application that functions as a sort of to-do list, similar to a travel bucket list but with a focus on food destinations.
- Employs the following technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Express.js, Mongoose, MongoDB, EJS

### Hangry App - github.com/cocampo0915/Hangry-App

- A web application that helps users decide on a meal to prepare based on a random generator, or through a criteria.
- Built with front-end technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX
- Responsive design implemented to allow application to be viewed on tablet or mobile devices, using CSS Flexbox.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Quality Control Support Analyst IV || March 2020 - August 2021

#### Grifols Diagnostics | San Diego, CA

- Performed routine testing utilizing various assays and techniques for the final release of products, consisting of various IVD assay kits testing for viruses, including SARS-CoV-2, HIV, HCV, HBV, Dengue, Parvo, Babesia.
- Managed QC Stability program and drove process improvements alongside management to improve workflow.

### Quality Control Analyst || July 2019 - March 2020

#### Takeda Pharmaceutical | Glendale, CA

- Conducted routine biological, chemical, and physical analyses on production material, following controlled test procedures, and critical to timely release of production schedule.
- Mastered and performed advanced assays requiring precise analytical skills and understanding of biological and chemical principles.

### Research Associate | July 2016 - Jun 2019

#### Hycor Biomedical | Garden Grove, CA

- Led internal research studies on a late-stage development medical device for the publication of white papers.
- Frequently generated reports and presentations for communication to executive leadership on progress of research studies.
- Acted as a subject matter expert for SDS-PAGE/Western Blot. Developed and implemented protocols for use by other lab personnel. Acted as lead trainer for this technique.

#### **EDUCATION**